Conor Cresswell

59 Titchfield Park Road, Fareham, Hampshire PO15 5RN

07808 274195 conorcresswell94@gmail.com

Portfolio Website: https://conorcresswell.github.io

Professional Summary

A self-motivated individual underpinned with a strong work ethic with an ambitious approach to life both professionally and personally. With two years of experience in Freelance Graphic Design and Illustration services using the Adobe Creative Suite with a focus on Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop and InDesign. Mixed in with a first-class undergraduate degree in Digital Media Design and undertaking a post-graduate degree in Digital Media Practice. A young, confident designer in their field who will always enjoy undertaking challenging and pushing projects without being afraid to do something different.

Key Skills

- · Confident ability to create vector illustrations using Adobe Illustrator
- · Strong ability in Adobe InDesign and Photoshop to create effective and informative documents
- Practical Experience in using HTML and CSS Frameworks to create one-page websites
- Experience in managing time and workload independently through Freelance work
- Confidence in presenting ideas to clients and team members

Work Experience

Sprechen Digital Marketing - Freelance Graphic Designer and Illustrator

(March 2015 to April 2017)

Duties

- Accountable for graphical elements for use in both print and digital design
- Created design documents to be used by the company and their clients
- · Accelerated productivity by diagnosing briefs and goals with clients independently
- · Collaborating with other team members on informative documents for clients

Bravo Post Production - Graphic Design and Animation Intern

(July 2015 to August 2015)

Duties

- Enhanced my own skills in developing animations using Adobe After Effects.
- Collaborated with industry professionals to create 2D Graphics.
- Integrated with co-workers to create storyboards for planned animations.
- Responsible for vector illustration files made using Adobe Illustrator

Education

University of Winchester

MA Digital Media Practice - Due to Finish Study in September 2017

(2016 - 2017)

Skills learned and tasks completed during this degree include...

- · Demonstrated knowledge of an effective brand identity by building brand guidelines
- Writing a case study on the effectiveness of prototyping software on obtaining user feedback
- Showcasing advanced skills in graphic design by creating logos, posters, and multi-page documents
- Engaging end-users with a prototype to gather user feedback using Adobe Experience Design
- Expanded my knowledge in HTML, CSS and JavaScript by learning to use the Bootstrap Framework

BA Digital Media Design - Graduated with First Class Honours

(2013 to 2016)

Skills learned and tasks completed during this degree include...

- Learning and understanding the basics of design theory through practical tasks.
- Collaborated with my peers in groups to execute real-world briefs with pre-designated clients.
- Furthering my skills in vector illustration using Adobe Illustrator software.
- Building working prototypes for websites and applications using basic HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Implementing gantt charts and objective lists to manage multiple projects simultaneously.

The Chalfonts Community College (2006 - 2013)

3 A-Levels: Photography (C), Applied ICT (C) and Design & Technology: Product Design 3D (E) 10 GCSEs grades A-C including English (B) and Maths (B) 1 Diploma grade B in Level 2 Creative and Media

References | References are available upon request.